{
    "id": "e3b7d5439a114ffab053f01dd2115046",
    "title": "Prepositions Or No Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let’s ……………………. your plans.",
            "description": "Discuss is followed by a direct object without any preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "discuss",
                "discuss about",
                "discuss on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "713e742e97c549569c16dd243cb45ba0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… a cousin of hers.",
            "description": "Marry is followed by a direct object without any preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "married",
                "married with",
                "married to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "630ded78fb0f4ec68345f6ac31b32cba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The baby …………………….. her mother.",
            "description": "Resemble is followed by a direct object without any preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "resembles",
                "resembles to",
                "resembles with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26604a2fed5e498587eaa37ad18c7ec8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget meeting her …………………….. afternoon.",
            "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning this or that.",
            "answers": [
                "on that",
                "that",
                "in that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f996b510df54afe8facbf1a05d77652"
        },
        {
            "question": "The conference is ………………………. Friday.",
            "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning this or that.",
            "answers": [
                "this",
                "on this",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9aac1a86ae164521ae5dcb3d0a91fa82"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ……………………….. Friday in February.",
            "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning one.",
            "answers": [
                "one",
                "on one",
                "at one"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ed9f3383874429e951d7cb2f44afa3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was up ……………………. night.",
            "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning all.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "on all",
                "in all night"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "024ccb0ce62a4d8a8f7b469d3a5a3d63"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie has agreed to come …………………….. morning.",
            "description": "Sometimes we leave out on before the names of the days of the week. ",
            "answers": [
                "Monday",
                "on Monday",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b599e0be0fef437384daa179c988d0c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He calls his mother three times ……………………. day.",
            "description": "No preposition is used in the expression …. times a day.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "in a",
                "on a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "982defd81a264311a0fdf996e9d9e00c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Private lessons cost 20 dollars ………………….. hour.",
            "description": "No preposition is used in this expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "for an",
                "in an",
                "an"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "61438999a8a6485d9098881504e5865e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. day is your interview?",
            "description": "In an informal style, we can leave out on before what day.",
            "answers": [
                "On what",
                "What",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d3b8c957a43440d5b0bd519bf50866f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. time does the train arrive?",
            "description": "What time sounds more natural than at what time. ",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "At what",
                "On what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49f49121c7bc4cc5b5640838cc836c96"
        }
    ]
}